[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question" : "English people celebrate this holiday on th 25th of December.",
    "answer": "christmas"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question" : "In what country is St Patrics day a national holiday.",
    "answer": "ireland"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question" : "During this season people can ski, skate, sledge, play snow balls.",
    "answer": "winter"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question" : "On what holiday do people put pumkins on the windowsills.",
    "answer": "halloween"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question" : "On this holiday children get chocolate eggs or rabbits.",
    "answer": "easter"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question" : "We can see small green leaves on the trees in this season.",
    "answer": "spring"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question" : "This is the hottest season of the year.",
    "answer": "summer"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question" : "What clothes do people wear in summer.",
    "answer": "light"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question" : "In this season leaves on the trees are red and yellow.",
    "answer": "autumn"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question" : "In Mearch there is a holiday for English â€¦",
    "answer": "women"
  }
]